Guide to the Elizabeth Long academic papers, 1978-2014 UA 355
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
Elizabeth Long academic papers
1978-2014
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas https://library.rice.edu/woodson
Long, Elizabeth
UA 355
10 Linear Feet (10 boxes)
This collection consisits of research files; course materials; selected student papers; documents related to the daily and annual business of the sociology department, including financial reports, departmental memos, faculty evaluations, and correspondence; and In addition there are drafts, typescripts, and published articles written by Elizabeth Long.
Biographical Note
Elizabeth Long is Professor of Sociology at Rice University. She majored in History at Stanford University, and worked for several years in publishing for Simon & Schuster and Alfred A. Knopf, Inc. in New York City. She completed her doctorate at Brandeis University in 1979, teaching Women's Studies and doing administrative work at Wellesley College and M.I.T. during graduate school. She joined the faculty at Rice University in 1978. She was chair of the department of Sociology at Rice University from 2004-2013.
Professor Long has published in the fields of cultural sociology, sociology of gender, the sociology of knowledge, qualitative sociology, and contemporary sociological theory, as well as in the interdisciplinary fields of American Studies, cultural studies, and women's studies. Her most recent book is Book Clubs: Women and the Uses of Reading in Everyday Life (University of Chicago Press, 2003). Her research has been funded by the National Endowment for the Humanities. She has served on several Editorial Boards, including Communication Review, Book Research Quarterly, and Socialist Review. She has also served as Chair of the Culture Section of the American Sociological Association, and on the Program Committee for the American Sociological Association and the American Studies Association. At Rice University, she has won several teaching awards, including the George R. Brown Award for Excellence in Teaching and the Julia Miles Chance Award for teaching excellence and gender sensitivity.
Excerpted from http://sociology.rice.edu/Content.aspx?id=125
Historical note
Although courses in sociology were being taught at Rice as far back as 1924, the sociology department did not become an autonomous unit at the university until 1971, when it split from the previous Department of Anthropology and Sociology, established ten years earlier. The department, though beginning with only four professors, grew to offer 15-20 courses in 2004, as well as many opportunities for research and publication.
Scope and Contents
These papers include research files, course materials, selected student papers, and documents related to the daily and annual business of the sociology department, including financial reports, departmental memos, faculty evaluations, and correspondence. In addition there are drafts, typescripts, and published articles written by Elizabeth Long.
Access restrictions
The materials in this collection are restricted due to the sensitive information contained therein. Materials will be restricted until 2054. Contact woodson@rice.edu for information. woodson@rice.edu or call 713-348-2586.
Conditions Governing Access
Stored off-site at the Library Service Center. Please request this material via woodson@rice.edu or call 713-348-2586.
Related Archival Materials
Rice University Sociology Department Records, 1975-2004, UA 139
Index Terms
Subjects
Universities and colleges; Sociology; Universities and colleges -- Administration; Research; Women
Document Types
publications; lecture notes; personal papers
Subjects (Corporations)
Rice University
- Series I. Subject Files - Numerical List, 183375
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains subject files organized numerically 1-158 by the creator. They have been organized to maintain the original order. An index to the files is located in folder 1. Course files located in this series may also be found in Series III: Course Files.
  - File Index, 2010; 184126 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Environment (2 folders), 184127 (Box 1, Folder 2-3)
  - Dean Correspondence, 184128 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Annual Report, 2002-05; 184129 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Strategic Planning, 2006-07; 184130 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Grant Administration, 2004-09; 184131 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Mellon Fellows Program, 1987, 2006; 184132 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Department Issues, 2003-2012; 184133 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Post Doctoral Program, 2002-2009; 184134 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Duncan Award, 2005-06; 184135 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Department Job Search and recruiting (3 folders), 184136 (Box 1, Folder 12-14)
  - Chairs Meetings, 184137 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Sociology Minor, 184138 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Travel Funds, 184139 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Department Retreat, 2006, 2010, 2012; 184140 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Century Scholars, 184141 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Doctoral Advising - Current, 184142 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - CORRUL, 184143 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Annual Report, 2005; 184144 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Annual Report, 2006; 184145 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - UT Department of Public Health, 184146 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Graduate Program - General (3 folders), 184147 (Box 1, Folder 25-27)
  - Department Meetings, 184148 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - SACS (2 folders), 184149 (Box 2, Folder 1, Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Handbook, 184150 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Matteson, Judy, 184151 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Lindsay, D. Michael (2 folders), 184152 (Box 2, Folder 4-5)
  - Long [Elizabeth], 184153 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Smith, Roland, 184154 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Klineberg, Stephen, 184155 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Kimbro, Rachel, 184156 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Bratter, Jenifer, 184157 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Emerson, Michael, 184158 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Heard, Holly (2 folders), 184159 (Box 2, Folder 12-13)
  - Garcia, Patsy, 184160 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Articles: US Military and the White House Fellowship, 184161 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Articles: The Circuit of Power, 185006 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Articles: Rethinking Gender Difference on Religion, 185007 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Professors, Student, and Sex: The View from this Side of the Desk, 185008 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Notes on a Perspective, 185009 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Annotated Bibliography: Mary Catherine Dillman, 185010 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Articles: Culture in Interaction, 185011 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Articles: Reading, Radio, and the Movies, 185012 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Articles: Cultural Topographies as System of Classification, 185013 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Articles: Using Fiction Sociologically, 185014 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Culture, Winter 2008; 185015 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Timothy Aubry Erica Jong's Textual Bulimia, 185016 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Timothy Aubry, Afghanistan Meets the Amazon, 185017 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Article Review, The Place of Villa Grimaldi in Chile's Democracy, 185018 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Toward a Qualitative Methodology of Audience Study, 185019 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - What Can We Hear after Post-Modernism?, 185020 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Junko Sano, Japanese Motherhood, 185021 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Emerson Long, 184162 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Articles, Harding, 184163 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Articles, Third Wave Feminism, 184164 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Leadership Series, Department Chair, 184165 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - V2C [Vision for the Second Century, RIce University], 184166 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Population Center, 184167 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Book Clubs, 184168 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Root & Branch, 184169 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Book Club Reviews, 184177 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Student Photos, 184178 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Diversity in the Academy, 184182 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Book Reading, 184184 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Articles, Lichtenstein, Bronwen, 184185 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Deconstructing Whiteness, 184179 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Energetic Sensibility, 184187 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Gender (2 folders), 184188 (Box 3, Folder 8-9)
  - Talks/Presentations, 184189 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Wall Hall Expenditures, 184190 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - External Review, 184193 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Department Information, 184194 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Gender Disparity, 184196 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Cambridge Handbook of Litearcy, 184197 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Syllabi, 184199 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Long - Awards, 184200 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Time Management, 184201 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Faculty Initiatives Fund, 184203 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Sociology & Culture ASA Section, 184204 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Sociology & Culture, 184206 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Fellowship Awards (2 folders), 184207 (Box 3, Folder 22-23)
  - Memorabilia, 184208 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Sociology 421, 184210 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Program for Study of Houston URC, 184211 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Minority Scholar Speaker Series, 184213 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Tapscott, Shirley, 184214 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - American Enterprise Institute, 184215 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Talks/Presentations - Other, 184217 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Welcome to Rice, 184218 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Personal, 184219 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - CSES, 184221 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - CSWGS (3 folders), 184222 (Box 4, Folder 2-4)
  - Gorman, Bridget, 184223 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Department History, 184224 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Department Faculty Leave & Evaluation Schedule, 184225 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - BIPP Envi/Sci/Religi/Soci Conference, 184226 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Reviews of Projects, MSS, etc, 184227 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Comer, Krista, 184228 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Piper Foundation, 184229 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Schilt, Kristen, 184230 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Chandler Davidson Fund, 184231 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Stone, Katherine, 184232 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - William T. Grant Foundation, 184233 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Environment: Readings, Sources (2 folders), 184234 (Box 4, Folder 16-17)
  - Environmental Justice, 184235 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Doctoral Advising - Former, 184236 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Murdock, Steven, 184237 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - McRobbie, Angela, 184238 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Fieldwork, 184239 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - UCSD Conference, 2007; 184240 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Beyond the Book Conference, 2007; 184241 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - History of the Book, Volumes IV and V (7 folders), 184242 (Box 5, Folder 1-3, Box 4, Folder 25-28)
  - DeLange Conference, 184243 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - ODC, 184244 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Religion, Science and Environment, 184245 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Feminism and print culture, 184246 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Ecklund, Elaine Howard - Spirituality & Scientists (4 folders), 184247 (Box 5, Folder 8-11)
  - Undergrad Independent Study - Former, 184250 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Grad Student Projects & PhDs, 184251 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - China Research & Scholarly Exchange, 184252 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Eckland, Elaine Howard (2 folders), 184253 (Box 5, Folder 15-16)
  - CSES Reading, 184248 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Green Urbanism, 184249 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Evalution: Colleagues, 184254 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Speaking Gigs, 184255 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Department Emeriti, 184256 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Patch Hires, 184257 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - IGEL, 184258 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - African-American Studies, 184259 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - China Trip, 2008; 184260 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Department Budget, 184261 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - School of Social Science, 184262 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Rice Leaders, 184263 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Mentoring, 184264 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Department Space, 185022 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - HERE projects, 184265 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Committees - Ex, Former, Old, 184266 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Independent Study Students - Former, 184267 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - SHARP, 184268 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Postdoc Research, 184269 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Hiring Process Diversity, 184270 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - HRC/FAP, 184271 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Finished Projects (2 folders), 184272 (Box 6, Folder 14-15)
  - Abandoned Research (2 folders), 184273 (Box 6, Folder 16-17)
  - Department Tenure & Evaluation, 184274 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Johnson, Richard, 184275 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Ecofeminism, 184276 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Center for Civic Engagement, 184277 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Houston Endowment, 184278 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Social Movements, 185023 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Slow Food, 184279 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - ENST 415 (3 folders), 184280 (Box 6, Folder 25, Box 7, Folder 1-2)
  - ENST 302/SOCI 304, 184290 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Self Study (2 folders), 184291 (Box 7, Folder 4-5)
  - Department Staff Hiring, 184292 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - University Finances, 184293 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - AASHE, 184294 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Radway, Janice, 184295 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Graduate Program Proposal (3 folders), 184296 (Box 7, Folder 10-12)
  - Graduate Program Curriculum, 184297 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Course Buy Outs, 184298 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Future Reading, 184299 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Salary, 184300 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Spiro, Lisa, 184301 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Students: Organization Advising, 184302 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Department: Teaching, 184303 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - IUR, 184304 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Department: Faculty Hiring, 184305 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Personal Contacts, 184306 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Long: University Funds, 184307 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Rice University - Baylor Merger, 184308 (Box 7, Folder 24)
- Series II. Current Files, 184309
  This series contains current files organized numerically by the creator. They have been organized to maintain the original order. An index to the files is located in folder 1.
  - Graduate Program - Provost Fellowship, 184310 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Enivornmental Film Course, 185024 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Floating Environmental Books, 184311 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Mobilizing Texts, 184312 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Environmental Focus Groups (2 folders), 184313 (Box 7, Folder 29-30)
  - ENST/SOCI 415, 184314 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - ENST 302/SOCI 304, 184315 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Biracial Memoirs, 184316 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Series III. Course Materials, 183376
  - SOCI 304 Fall 2008, 184317 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - SOCI 304 Fall 2009, 184318 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - SOCI 304 Fall 2012, 184319 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - SOCI 304 Fall 2013, 184601 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - SOCI 306 Fall 1998, 184320 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - SOCI 306 Fall 1999, 184321 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - SOCI 306 Fall 2003, 184322 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - SOCI 359 Fall 2002, 184323 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - SOCI 395 Spring 2005, 184324 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - SOCI 395 Spring 2006, 184325 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - SOCI 415 Spring 2008, 184326 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - SOCI 415 Spring 2009, 184327 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - SOCI 421 Spring 1991, 184328 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - SOCI 421 Spring 1997, 184329 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - SOCI 421 Spring 1998, 184330 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - SOCI 421 Spring 1999, 184331 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - SOCI 421 Spring 2001, 184332 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - SOCI 421 Fall 2001, 184333 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - SOCI 421 Fall 2002, 184334 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - SOCI 421 Spring 2003, 184335 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - SOCI 421 Fall 2004, 184336 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - SOCI 421 Sample Final Papers Fall 2004, 184337 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - SOCI 421 Sample Journal Entries, 184338 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - SOCI 421 Fall 2006, 184339 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - SOCI 445 Spring 2004, 184340 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - SOCI 445 Fall 2005, 184341 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Culture of Sociology syllabus, 184342 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Sociology of the Internet, 184343 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - American Dreams and Popular Novel Reviews, 184344 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Teaching issues, 184345 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Course CDs, 184346 (Box 8, Folder 34)
    General
    SOCI 359, 323, 395, 408, 421, 445, Century Scholars
- Series IV. Projects, Published materials, and Talks, 183377
  - Graduate work, 184348
    - Anti-Smelser or the Poverty of Parsonianism, 184955 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Austin Hippie-Red Community, 184352 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - The Beginnings of Inequality between Men and Women: A study of the Bushmen and Arunta, 184355 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - The Chinese Cultural Revolution in Developmental Perspective, 184353 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Contemporary Reformulations of Marxist Theory, 184956 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Contemporary Women: An Interdisciplinary Perspective - Extra Departmental 210 course, 184359 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Heroic Domesticity: Women's Place in American Bestsellers, 1945-1975, 184349 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - The Intimate Dialectic: Feminism and the Works of Virginia Woolf, 184351 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Lives on left, 184357 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Memory Paper, 184350 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - "On Gurr's 'A Casual Model of Civil Strife'", 184354 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Portrayals of Women and the Family in American Bestsellers, 1945-1975, 184957 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - The Romance of the Self: The emergent formula of the independent woman in popular fiction, 184358 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Search for Funding for Women's Reading Group Research (2 folders), 1984-1990; 184360 (Box 9, Folder 14-15)
    - Sexuality, Ambition, and the Place of Women in Postwar Popular Literature, 184958 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Talking to people about their marriages, 184356 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Published Works, 184361
    - Affluence and After: Themes of Success in American Best-Selling novels, 1945-75, 184362 (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - The Book as Mass Commodity: the audience perspective, Spring 1987; 184363 (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - The Cultural Meaning of Concentration in Publishing, 1985-86; 184364 (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - Engaging Sociology and Cultural Studies: Disciplinarity and Social Change, introduction to From Sociology to Cultural Studies: New Perspectives, 1997; 184368 (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - Feminism and Cultural Studies, 1989; 184365 (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - Literature as a Spur to Collective Action, 2004; 184367 (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - Poetics Today, 184953 (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - Reading Groups and the Postmodern Crisis of Cultural Authority, 1987; 184370 (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - The Reproduction of Motherhood, Spring 1980; 184366 (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - Review: J. Mitchell, Psychoanalysis and Feminism, 1974; 184372 (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - Textual Interpretation as Collective Action, 1992; 184369 (Box 9, Folder 28)
    - Women, Reading, and Cultural Authority: Some Implications, Fall 1986; 184371 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Talks, 184373
    - Beyond the Mass Audience, MIT Communications Forum, September 29, 1988; 184381 (Box 9, Folder 30)
    - Collective Action, Princeton, 1989; 184375 (Box 9, Folder 31)
    - Conference on Ethnographic & Qualitative Research in Education, June 6, 1991; 184374 (Box 9, Folder 32)
    - Culture, Gender, and Community, 1989; 184376 (Box 9, Folder 33)
    - Culture and Gender: A Sociological Viewpoint presented at American Studies Association, October 1988; 184377 (Box 9, Folder 34)
    - IGEL, August 1997; 184954 (Box 9, Folder 35)
    - Investigating Interpretative Communities: Preliminary Observations on Women's Reading Groups, April 1982; 184379 (Box 9, Folder 36)
    - Loving Books in the Digital Age, Why Books?, October 28-29, 2010; 184380 (Box 9, Folder 37)
    - Mukiyi Email Conference, May 1994; 184382 (Box 9, Folder 38)
    - Reading Together - Women's Book Clubs in Texas, Texas Women's University, November 12, 1996; 184383 (Box 9, Folder 39)
    - Reading Together: Women's Reading Groups and American Culture, Harvard, October 1997; 184378 (Box 9, Folder 40)
    - Proto talks about the book, 184384 (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - Ongoing projects, 184385
    - Between Public Culture & Private Lives: Women's Reading Groups and the Making of the Middle Class, 184387 (Box 9, Folder 42)
    - Buddhism and the body (2 folders), 2000; 184388 (Box 9, Folder 43-44)
    - A Decade of Lessons from Connecting Campus Greening with the Classroom at Rice University, 184386 (Box 9, Folder 45)
    - Designing Reader Studies, 1981; 184389 (Box 9, Folder 46)
    - Feminism and Foucault (2 folders), 184390 (Box 9, Folder 47-48)
    - Gender and Power, 184391 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Library History, 184392 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Local Reading Groups and American Literature Culture, 1986; 184393 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Reading Story, 184998 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Readings at the Grassroots, 1987; 184394 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Recycling Alone research, 184396 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Spirituality - Literature review suggestions, 184397 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Spirituality - Coding on categories of Religious and Spirituality, 184398 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Spiritual but not religious (3 folders), 184399 (Box 10, Folder 9-11)
    - Women of Science Fiction, 184395 (Box 10, Folder 12)
- Series V. Administrative Files, Periodicals, 184347
  - American Studies, November 1995; 184970 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Beth Shapiro Award, 2008-09; 184971 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Sabina Bharwani, 184972 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence, 2009-2013, n.d.; 184973 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - James Elliott, 184974 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Laura Essenburg, 184975 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Caroline Gill, 184976 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Aundrea Matthews, 184977 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - New Faculty Senate, 2011; 184978 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Non-urgent items, 184979 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Notes, 184980 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - James Phillips, 184981 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Poverty, Justice, and Human Capabilities, 184982 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Proposal for the Hobby Center, 184983 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Quantitative Methodologist Job Description, 184984 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Rhonda Ragsdale, 184985 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Religion and Public Life, 2012; 184986 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Research Methods, 184987 (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Rice IRB Application, 184988 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Rice University Space Utilization, 2008; 184989 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Sennett, [Richard], 184990 (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - S.H.A.R.E, 184991 (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Sustainable Rice Group, 184992 (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - Techniques of Interviewing, 184993 (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - Ruth Lopez Turley, 184994 (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - Brenda Watt, 184995 (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - Yuanyuan Zhang, 184996 (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - Magazine: Cosmopolitan, September 1953; 184961 (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - Magazine: Ms., December 1979; 184962 (Box 10, Folder 41)
  - Magazine: The New York Times Magazine, April 20, 2008; 184963 (Box 10, Folder 42)
  - Magazine: "The True Story of John/Joan," Rolling Stone, December 11, 1997; 184964 (Box 10, Folder 43)
  - Magazine: The Saturday Evening Post, December 22-29, 1962; 184965 (Box 10, Folder 44)
  - Magazine: Time, March 9, 1992; 184966 (Box 10, Folder 45)
  - Magazine: Trans action, Vol. 8, number 1/2, November-December 1970; 184968 (Box 10, Folder 46)
  - Magazine: Utne Reader, May/June 1993; 184967 (Box 10, Folder 47)
  - Report: 1980 Virginia Slims American Women's Opinion Poll, 184969 (Box 10, Folder 48)
  - CDs: Desktop backup (5 CDs), 184997 (Box 10, Folder 49)
  - Engagement Book, 1990; 185025 (Box 10, Folder 50)